Sleep has gone from being a sleepy topic to one that is now heavily studied by top-tier researchers.
لقد انتقل النوم من كونه موضوعًا مملًّا إلى موضوعٍ يُدرَس الآن بشكل مكثف من قِبل باحثين من الطراز الأوّل.
While there is still some mystery surrounding why humans need so much sleep,
ورغم أن هناك بعض الغموض لا يزال يحيط بالسبب الذي يجعل البشر بحاجة إلى قدر كبير من النوم،
there really is no mystery about how essential it is to get enough.
فلا يوجد أي غموض حقًّا حول مدى أهمية الحصول على قسط كافٍ منه.
Yet, when I talk with my clients and ask them how they're sleeping,
ومع ذلك، عندما أتحدث مع عملائي وأسألهم عن جودة نومهم،
about half of the time I'm met with, I roll size and visible frustration.
أجد أن حوالي نصفهم يُظهرون علامات الإحباط الواضحة والمرئية.
Many people simply aren't sleeping well.
الكثير من الناس ببساطة لا ينامون جيدًا.
Hi, I'm Melanie Luther, I'm a certified nutrition specialist and a licensed dietitian nutritionist.
مرحباً، أنا ميلاني لوثر، أخصائية تغذية معتمدة وأخصائية تغذية مرخصة.
Level up your sleep is a thoughtfully designed nutritional supplement that may help support better sleep.
"Level Up Your Sleep" هو مكمّل غذائي صُمّم بعناية وقد يساعد في دعم نوم أفضل.
It contains magnesium by glycinate, a highly bio-available, well absorbed form of this essential mineral.
ويحتوي على مغنيسيوم جليسِينات، وهو شكلٌ من هذا المعدن الأساسي يتميّز بامتصاص عالي وتوافر حيوي ممتاز.
Research suggests that magnesium by glycinate may modestly improve sleep quality
تشير الأبحاث إلى أن مغنيسيوم الجليسِينات قد يحسّن جودة النوم بشكل متواضع
and support both falling asleep and staying asleep.
ويدعم كلًّا من الدخول في النوم والاستمرار فيه.
Without adequate magnesium, it's incredibly difficult for the nervous system to relax and turn off at night.
فبدون كمية كافية من المغنيسيوم، يصبح من الصعب جدًّا على الجهاز العصبي الاسترخاء وإيقاف نشاطه ليلاً.
L-fianian is a non-essential amino acid that helps to ease the mind.
L-ثيانين هو حمض أميني غير أساسي يساعد في تهدئة العقل.
It supports the transition from the active brain wave states of alertness and problem solving
إذ يدعم الانتقال من حالات موجات الدماغ النشطة المرتبطة باليقظة وحل المشكلات
into the alpha state associated with relaxation and meditation.
إلى حالة ألفا المرتبطة بالاسترخاء والتأمل.
A state much more conducive for sleeping.
وهي حالة أكثر ملاءمةً بكثير للنوم.
Many people find it helps you quiet that mental chatter that seems to get louder
يجد الكثيرون أنه يساعد في تهدئة ثرثرة العقل الداخلية التي تبدو وكأنها تزداد صوتًا
the moment our heads hit the pillow.
في اللحظة التي تلامس فيها رؤوسنا الوسادة.
Ashragand is another valuable addition to this formula.
والأشواقاندا (Ashwagandha) إضافةٌ قيمة أخرى لهذه التركيبة.
A meta-analysis of five randomized controlled trials involving over 400 participants
فقد وجد تحليل تلوي لخمس دراسات عشوائية محكومة شملت أكثر من 400 مشارك
found a small but significant improvement in overall sleep with the greatest benefit seen
تحسّنًا بسيطًا لكنه ذو دلالة إحصائية في جودة النوم عمومًا، مع أكبر فائدة لوحظت
in individuals experiencing insomnia.
بين الأفراد الذين يعانون من الأرق.
Its angelitic properties, meaning it's ability to calm feelings of anxiety, may also
كما أن خصائصه المهدئة—أي قدرته على تقليل مشاعر القلق—قد تساعد أيضًا
support sleep in those experiencing chronic stress.
في دعم النوم لدى من يعانون من التوتر المزمن.
Last but not least is Vitamin B6.
وأخيرًا وليس آخرًا، هناك فيتامين B6.
This essential B vitamin is required for the production of key sleep-related neurotransmitters,
هذا الفيتامين البسيط ضروري لإنتاج النواقل العصبية الأساسية المرتبطة بالنوم،
including melatonin, GABA, serotonin and dopamine.
بما في ذلك الميلاتونين، GABA، السيروتونين، والدوبامين.
It's also important to know that regular alcohol consumption and high caffeine intake
ومن المهم أيضًا أن تعرف أن استهلاك الكحول بانتظام وتناول كميات عالية من الكافيين
can negatively impact vitamin B6 status which may contribute to difficulty falling or staying
يمكن أن يؤثرا سلبًا على مستويات فيتامين B6، مما قد يساهم في صعوبة الدخول في النوم أو الاستمرار فيه.
asleep.
.
Additionally, I think it's important to know that supplementing with Vitamin B6 may increase
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، أعتقد أنه من المهم أن تعرف أن تناول مكمّلات فيتامين B6 قد يزيد
dream vividness and recall.
من وضوح الأحلام وقدرتك على تذكّرها.
Thank you so much.
شكرًا جزيلًا لكم.